[
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_039",
        "question": "A 62-year-old white man with a past medical history of latent tuberculosis, vitiligo, and psoriasis presents for follow-up for treatment of psoriasis. <br>- The patient’s psoriasis has proven refractory to numerous treatments over the years, so he began treatment with secukinumab, a monoclonal antibody against interleukin-17A. <br>- After 2 months of therapy, the patient reports new-onset tongue pain. <br>- Physical examination demonstrates an erythematous, edematous, diamond-shaped plaque on the posterior dorsum of the patient’s tongue.",
        "option1": "Geographic tongue",
        "option2": "Lichen planus",
        "option3": "Median rhomboid glossitis",
        "option4": "Secondary syphilis",
        "correct_option": 1,
        "ai_prediction": 4,
        "ai_confidence": "48%",
        "ai_is_correct": false
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_030",
        "question": "The patient is a 38-year-old Hispanic woman who presents with a 1-year history of a very pruritic rash over her interscapular area. <br>- On examination, she has a circular area of slightly hyperpigmented macules in the interscapular region. <br>- The patient complains of pruritus but no pain in the area of the rash. <br>- The patient has no other medical problems and has no systemic symptoms. <br>- She has no relevant social or family history and does not take any medications.",
        "option1": "Paresthetica",
        "option2": "Macular amyloidosis",
        "option3": "Prurigo nodularis",
        "option4": "Lichen amyloidosis",
        "correct_option": 1,
        "ai_prediction": 4,
        "ai_confidence": "46%",
        "ai_is_correct": false
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_023",
        "question": "The patient is a 12-year-old Hispanic girl who presents with a 6-month history of nail dystrophy involving all of her fingernails. <br>- On examination, all 10 of her fingernails exhibit longitudinal ridging, pitting, fragility, thinning, and distal notching. <br>- The patient’s mother is very concerned about the cosmesis of her daughter’s nails. <br>- The patient has no systemic symptoms. <br>- On review of systems, the patient’s mother noted that her daughter has started to develop circular patches of hair loss that appear to resolve on their own. <br>- The patient has no relevant social or family history and does not take any medications.",
        "option1": "Trachyonychia",
        "option2": "Brittle nails",
        "option3": "Lichen planus",
        "option4": "Psoriasis",
        "correct_option": 2,
        "ai_prediction": 2,
        "ai_confidence": "46%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_002",
        "question": "An 8-year-old male child is brought to the clinic for the third time in 4 months presenting with red-brown papules with an overlying mica-like scale on the ventral side of his arms and legs. <br>- His medical and family histories are otherwise unremarkable. <br>- His mother states that when the macules and papules go away, the skin where the lesions were previously located is typically lighter than before.",
        "option1": "Langerhans cell histiocytosis",
        "option2": "Varicella",
        "option3": "Pityriasis lichenoides et varioliformis acuta",
        "option4": "Gianotti-Crosti syndrome",
        "correct_option": 4,
        "ai_prediction": 4,
        "ai_confidence": "88%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_055",
        "question": "A 50-year-old woman presents with a 5-day history of progressive, painful rash involving her face, trunk, extremities, nasal tip, and ears, in addition to fever and arthralgia. <br>- She admits to a history of polysubstance use and states that her last use was a week prior to symptom onset. <br>- She denies a history of autoimmune disease or recent travel. <br>- Examination reveals retiform purpura with areas of necrosis and bullae formation. <br>- Urine toxicology screening is positive for cocaine, and laboratory findings include leukopenia and an elevated erythrocyte sedimentation rate (70 mm/h).",
        "option1": "Levamisole-induced antineutrophil cytoplasmic antibody vasculitis",
        "option2": "Disseminated intravascular coagulation",
        "option3": "Warfarin-induced skin necrosis",
        "option4": "Tinea incognito",
        "correct_option": 4,
        "ai_prediction": 3,
        "ai_confidence": "41%",
        "ai_is_correct": false
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_117",
        "question": "A 40-year-old female presents with a recurrent skin eruption on her nose and cheeks for 2 years. <br>- These lesions appears usually in the summer following excessive sun exposure, and disappears without scarring. <br>- She has complains about arthritis and chronic fatigue. <br>- She denies muscle weakness. <br>- Physical exam reveals butterfly-shaped erythematous plaques over the malar area, non-scarring alopecia and oral ulcers.",
        "option1": "Systemic lupus erythematosus",
        "option2": "Rosacea",
        "option3": "Dermatomyositis",
        "option4": "Seborrheic dermatitis",
        "correct_option": 1,
        "ai_prediction": 4,
        "ai_confidence": "43%",
        "ai_is_correct": false
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_004",
        "question": "A 20-year-old woman presents to the clinic with a circular hypopigmented lesion on her right cheek. <br>- The patient stated that she used to have a mole in the same location. <br>- Over time she noticed a white area around the mole that enlarged to the current size of the lesion. <br>- After a few months she noticed the mole in the center of the lesion had disappeared. <br>- On further questioning, she denies any personal or family history of skin cancer.",
        "option1": "Melanoma",
        "option2": "Vitiligo",
        "option3": "Halo nevus",
        "option4": "Dysplastic nevus",
        "correct_option": 1,
        "ai_prediction": 1,
        "ai_confidence": "63%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_050",
        "question": "A healthy 15-year-old girl presents with a solitary, asymptomatic lesion on her back. <br>- The lesion has been present since birth but has enlarged over the past 2 years. <br>- She denies association with previous trauma and irritation. <br>- Examination reveals multiple, comedo-like openings filled with dark lamellate keratinocyte plugs grouped in a linear distribution over a slightly hypotrophic area of 3 cm by 7 cm. <br>- Dermoscopy revealed numerous circular and barrel-shaped homogenous areas in dark-brown shades with remarkable keratin plugs.",
        "option1": "Familial dyskeratotic comedones",
        "option2": "Trichofolliculoma",
        "option3": "Nevus comedonicus",
        "option4": "Segmental acne",
        "correct_option": 1,
        "ai_prediction": 1,
        "ai_confidence": "52%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_112",
        "question": "A 10-year-old male presents with non-blanchable palpable purple papules on both legs for a week. <br>- Sore throat preceded the skin lesions. <br>- His parents deny any other history of infectious diseases or new medications. <br>- The boy complains about abdominal pain and trouble walking. <br>- His vitals are stable. <br>- Physical exam reveals red and swollen ankles on top of palpable purpura on both legs.",
        "option1": "IgA vasculitis",
        "option2": "Thrombocytopenic purpura",
        "option3": "Bacterial endocarditis",
        "option4": "Meningococcemia",
        "correct_option": 1,
        "ai_prediction": 1,
        "ai_confidence": "56%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_009",
        "question": "A 43-year-old African American woman presents to the clinic with irritative lesions in the folds of her abdomen and in her genital region as well as painful ulcers in her oral mucosa. <br>- The patient reports noticing some flaccid blisters in addition to the lesions she presents with. <br>- On examination, erythematous, vegetative lesions are found. <br>- She states that the affected areas are painful but not pruritic. <br>- She has a previous history of herpes simplex virus (HSV).",
        "option1": "Pemphigus vegetans",
        "option2": "Squamous cell carcinoma",
        "option3": "Bowen’s disease",
        "option4": "Proderma gangraneosum",
        "correct_option": 2,
        "ai_prediction": 2,
        "ai_confidence": "43%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_111",
        "question": "A 60-year-old female presents with a non-healing painful ulcer on her right leg for 4 months. <br>- She says she first noticed it after she accidentally bumped into a chair. <br>- She is known for rheumatoid arthritis and hypertension, and has taken methotrexate and bisoprolol for years. <br>- According to the patient, oral antibiotics and wound debridement have only increase the size of the ulcer. <br>- Physical exam reveals a 5x5 cm fibrinous ulcer with violaceous undermined borders on her right shin.",
        "option1": "Traumatic wound",
        "option2": "Pyoderma grangrenosum",
        "option3": "Arterial ulcer",
        "option4": "Venous ulcer",
        "correct_option": 4,
        "ai_prediction": 4,
        "ai_confidence": "53%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_047",
        "question": "A 13-year-old girl presents with a cystic lesion that has been on her forearm for several years. <br>- Concerned about the lesion, she reports that it may have grown slightly larger in the past year and it is intermittently painful. <br>- More recently, a second similar lesion has appeared in close proximity. <br>- She denies any other suspicious lesions elsewhere on her skin. <br>- Her family history is negative for skin cancer, and she reports no other medical conditions. <br>- Physical examination reveals two well-defined 6-mm nodules that are rubbery, slightly tender, and pink on the right proximal ventral forearm. <br>- The overlying skin is intact, and there is no associated adenopathy.",
        "option1": "Glomus tumor",
        "option2": "Angiolipoma",
        "option3": "Spiradenoma",
        "option4": "neuroma",
        "correct_option": 4,
        "ai_prediction": 4,
        "ai_confidence": "50%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_100",
        "question": "A 54-year-old woman presents with 2 years of gradual hair thinning. <br>- She says that her mother also experienced hair thinning starting in her 50s. <br>- She denies scalp itch. <br>- She denies clumps of hair coming out in the shower or on her pillow. <br>- She denies any preceding stressful life events. <br>- She denies wearing her hair in tight braids. <br>- She denies loss of eyebrows or eyelashes. <br>- Physical examination reveals frontotemporal hair thinning without scarring.",
        "option1": "Alopecia areata",
        "option2": "Central centrifugal cicatricial alopecia",
        "option3": "Androgenetic alopecia",
        "option4": "Telogen effluvium",
        "correct_option": 1,
        "ai_prediction": 1,
        "ai_confidence": "56%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_052",
        "question": "A healthy 12-month-old infant girl presents with a yellowish-orange papule on the right upper extremity. <br>- Her mother first noticed this lesion approximately 6 months earlier. <br>- It has never bled, ulcerated, or formed blisters. <br>- The infant does not scratch the lesion nor appears otherwise bothered by it. <br>- However, when the lesion is rubbed, it appears to swell and turn bright red. <br>- On physical examination, there is a soft, oval-shaped, yellowish papule with a peripheral rim of erythema on the right extensor forearm.",
        "option1": "Pseudomonas nail infection",
        "option2": "Solitary mastocytoma",
        "option3": "Epidermolysis bullosa",
        "option4": "Bullous arthropod bites",
        "correct_option": 1,
        "ai_prediction": 2,
        "ai_confidence": "60%",
        "ai_is_correct": false
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_013",
        "question": "A 24-year-old Caucasian woman presented with intermittent, inflammatory papulopustules and nodules on the face, neck, chest, and back. <br>- The lesions would appear 1 week premenstrually and resolve 1 week postmenstrually with normal menstrual cycles. <br>- She has a history of adolescent acne that is only responsive to isotretinoin 6 years ago. <br>- Examination revealed scarring and postinflammatory hyperpigmentation diffusely on her face.",
        "option1": "Acne vulgaris",
        "option2": "Alopecia",
        "option3": "Rosacea",
        "option4": "Acanthosis nigricans",
        "correct_option": 2,
        "ai_prediction": 2,
        "ai_confidence": "43%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    }
]